<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bestlists | High Quality Twitter Accounts, Blogs, Podcasts and Resources</title>
    <link>https://bestlists.top/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bestlists | High Quality Twitter Accounts, Blogs, Podcasts and Resources</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Alex Carter</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:01:24 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://bestlists.top/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Twitter Accounts Value Investing to Follow</title>
      <link>https://bestlists.top/10-best-twitter-accounts-value-investing-to-follow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:01:24 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bestlists.top/10-best-twitter-accounts-value-investing-to-follow/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2024-04-25&#xA;In the world of investing, value investing stands out as a strategy focused on finding stocks that appear underpriced relative to their intrinsic value. Social media, especially Twitter, has become a vital platform for sharing insights and strategies, making it easier than ever to access advice from leading experts. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to deepen your understanding of value investing, here are the 10 best Twitter accounts to follow on X (formerly known as Twitter).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Mauboussin, Bill Gurley - Putting Theory into Practice</title>
      <link>https://bestlists.top/Daily-Digest-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:29:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bestlists.top/Daily-Digest-04/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2024-04-24&#xA;In a compelling dialogue, Patrick O&amp;rsquo;Shaughnessy engages with Bill Gurley and Michael Mauboussin, distinguished experts in their fields, on a variety of insightful subjects. Here&amp;rsquo;s a refined summary of their key discussions:&#xA;AI&amp;rsquo;s Impact: The conversation begins with an exploration of artificial intelligence&amp;rsquo;s potential to either bolster industry leaders or pave the way for innovative newcomers. Investing in AI: Gurley stresses the necessity for a clear understanding of AI&amp;rsquo;s current capabilities and its implications for investment strategies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily Digest #03: Michael Mauboussin on Valuation Multiples</title>
      <link>https://bestlists.top/Daily-Digest-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:11:44 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bestlists.top/Daily-Digest-03/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2024-04-24&#xA;The article from Consilient Observer by Michael J. Mauboussin and Dan Callahan, published on April 23, 2024.&#xA;It focuses on the effectiveness and limitations of valuation multiples like P/E (price-earnings) and EV/EBITDA (enterprise value to earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization) in financial analysis.&#xA;It highlights a common practice among analysts of using valuation multiples for pricing companies rather than delving into a detailed valuation based on the discounted cash flow (DCF) model,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily Digest #01: Modeling life, underatanding power and Gautam Baid talk</title>
      <link>https://bestlists.top/Daily-Digest-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:49:03 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bestlists.top/Daily-Digest-01/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2024-04-22&#xA;1.Modeling Life: Oscillation Link&#xA;Bullet points:&#xA;• Oscillatory behavior refers to a cyclical system behavior that occurs in the human body.&#xA;• The hypothalamus (H), pituitary gland (P), and gonads (G) are involved in a hormonal feedback loop.&#xA;• There is a negative feedback loop where increased gonadal hormones inhibit hypothalamus hormones.&#xA;• This HPG axis can be modeled using differential equations with sigmoid functions.&#xA;• Oscillations arise from time delays in the feedback loop and steep negative feedback curves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily Digest #02: The minimalist entrepreneur Course, RBS and VIC</title>
      <link>https://bestlists.top/Daily-Digest-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:20:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bestlists.top/Daily-Digest-02/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2024-04-23&#xA;1. The Minimalist Entrepreneur Course Link&#xA;The Minimalist Entrepreneur Course, taught by Sahil Lavingia, aims to help aspiring entrepreneurs learn the principles of minimalist entrepreneurship.&#xA;2.Redfield, Blonsky &amp;amp; Starinsky Link&#xA;Redfield, Blonsky &amp;amp; Starinsky, LLC is an investment management firm that specializes in value investing and portfolio construction. Their website offers a variety of useful links and notes.&#xA;3. Value Investors Club Link&#xA;Value Investors Club (VIC) is an exclusive online investment club that aims to bring together top investors who share their best investment ideas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://bestlists.top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 19:27:08 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bestlists.top/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Alex Carter.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m the curator of BestLists.top dedicated to collecting high-quality Twitter/X accounts, blogs, podcasts and online resources.&#xA;I write on Medium.&#xA;If you come across any exceptional online resources, feel free to drop me a line via email at iamalexcarter@proton.me.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s connect and explore the digital landscape together!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Writings</title>
      <link>https://bestlists.top/writings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 19:27:08 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bestlists.top/writings/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s Essential Reads Daily Digest #01: Modeling life, underatanding power and Gautam Baid&amp;rsquo;s talk Daily Digest #02: The minimalist entrepreneur Course, RBS and VIC Daily Digest #03: Michael Mauboussin on Valuation Multiples Daily Digest #04: Michael Mauboussin, Bill Gurley - Putting Theory into Practice Best Twitter Accounts 10 Best Value Investing Twitter Accounts to Follow on X </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
